[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What makes the Vienna bread so light and airy?", "correct_answer": "Steam is used during baking.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "The dough is aerated.", "Lots of baking soda is added."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the scientific classification of animals, what does the term Dinosauria signify?", "correct_answer": "A superorder", "incorrect_answers": ["A family", "A genus", "A kingdom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the tests that Jeff was given in Saw III?", "correct_answer": "rack, freezer room, intestine pool", "incorrect_answers": ["classroom, angel, rack", "intestine pool, flammable jelly, razor wire maze", "needle pit, furnace, razor box"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Milk should not be exposed to strong light.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What major geographical feature is located at 23.5 degrees North latitude?", "correct_answer": "The Tropic of Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["The Equator", "The Arctic Circle", "The Tropic of Capricorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed sports agent Jerry Maguire in the 1996 movie Jerry Maguire?", "correct_answer": "Tom Cruise", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Affleck", "Matt Damon", "Tobey Maguire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What state was affected by the most powerful earthquake recorded in U.S. history prior to 2000?", "correct_answer": "Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "California", "Nebraska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sleepers, what was the name of the guard who was Group Leader of the boys while they were at the Wilkinson Home for boys?", "correct_answer": "Nokes", "incorrect_answers": ["Addison", "Styler", "Ferguson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 63rd Academy Awards ceremony in 1991, this 1990 movie received the Academy Award for Best Picture.", "correct_answer": "Dances with Wolves", "incorrect_answers": ["The Godfather Part III", "Ghost", "Awakenings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the word in Jewish folklore for a spirit that inhabits the soul and body of a dead person.", "correct_answer": "Dybbuk", "incorrect_answers": ["Dibbenhook", "DBennior", "Daven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Microraptor, the smallest known non-avian dinosaur, inhabited this modern day area during the early Cretaceous Period 130-125.5 million years ago.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Madagascar", "Australia", "Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Cio-Cio-San, a character in Giacomo Puccinis opera, Madame Butterfly ?", "correct_answer": "15", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "19", "21"]}]